[
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "When Eisenhower was elected President in 1952, he believed hiring practices and anti-discrimination laws should be decided by the states, although the administration gradually continued to desegregate the Armed Forces and the federal government.:50 The President also established the Government Contract Committee in 1953, which \"conducted surveys of the racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors\".:50\u201351 The committee, chaired by Vice President Richard Nixon, had minimal outcomes in that they imposed the contractors with the primary responsibility of desegregation within their own companies and corporations.:51",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the purpose of the Government Contract Committee?",
            "choices": [
                "Conducted Surveys Of The Racial Composition Of Federal Employees And Tax-Supported Contractors",
                "Committee",
                "50",
                "51"
            ],
            "answer": "Conducted surveys of the racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "When Eisenhower was elected President in 1952, he believed hiring practices and anti-discrimination laws should be decided by the states, although the administration gradually continued to desegregate the Armed Forces and the federal government.:50 The President also established the Government Contract Committee in 1953, which \"conducted surveys of the racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors\".:50\u201351 The committee, chaired by Vice President Richard Nixon, had minimal outcomes in that they imposed the contractors with the primary responsibility of desegregation within their own companies and corporations.:51",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "How many years after Eisenhower was elected President, how many years after the Government Contract Committee was established?",
            "choices": [
                "1953",
                "1848",
                "1990",
                "1936"
            ],
            "answer": "1953"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "When Eisenhower was elected President in 1952, he believed hiring practices and anti-discrimination laws should be decided by the states, although the administration gradually continued to desegregate the Armed Forces and the federal government.:50 The President also established the Government Contract Committee in 1953, which \"conducted surveys of the racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors\".:50\u201351 The committee, chaired by Vice President Richard Nixon, had minimal outcomes in that they imposed the contractors with the primary responsibility of desegregation within their own companies and corporations.:51",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "How many years did the Government Contract Committee run?",
            "choices": [
                "1990",
                "1953",
                "1936",
                "1848"
            ],
            "answer": "1953"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "When Eisenhower was elected President in 1952, he believed hiring practices and anti-discrimination laws should be decided by the states, although the administration gradually continued to desegregate the Armed Forces and the federal government.:50 The President also established the Government Contract Committee in 1953, which \"conducted surveys of the racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors\".:50\u201351 The committee, chaired by Vice President Richard Nixon, had minimal outcomes in that they imposed the contractors with the primary responsibility of desegregation within their own companies and corporations.:51",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the name of the committee that imposed desegregation on contractors?",
            "choices": [
                "Government Contract Committee",
                "51",
                "50",
                "President"
            ],
            "answer": "Government contract committee"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "When Eisenhower was elected President in 1952, he believed hiring practices and anti-discrimination laws should be decided by the states, although the administration gradually continued to desegregate the Armed Forces and the federal government.:50 The President also established the Government Contract Committee in 1953, which \"conducted surveys of the racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors\".:50\u201351 The committee, chaired by Vice President Richard Nixon, had minimal outcomes in that they imposed the contractors with the primary responsibility of desegregation within their own companies and corporations.:51",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "Who did the Government Contract Committee survey?",
            "choices": [
                "President",
                "The Racial Composition Of Federal Employees And Tax-Supported Contractors",
                "50",
                "51"
            ],
            "answer": "The racial composition of federal employees and tax-supported contractors"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "According to this theory, the conditions for the truth of a sentence as well as the sentences themselves are part of a metalanguage. So, for example, the sentence \"Snow is white\" is true if and only if snow is white. Although many philosophers have interpreted, and continue to interpret, Tarski's theory as a deflationary theory, Popper refers to it as a theory in which \"is true\" is replaced with \"corresponds to the facts\". He bases this interpretation on the fact that examples such as the one described above refer to two things: assertions and the facts to which they refer. He identifies Tarski's formulation of the truth conditions of sentences as the introduction of a \"metalinguistic predicate\" and distinguishes the following cases:",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is Tarski's theory called?",
            "choices": [
                "Facts",
                "Conditions",
                "Refer",
                "Deflationary Theory"
            ],
            "answer": "Deflationary theory"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "According to this theory, the conditions for the truth of a sentence as well as the sentences themselves are part of a metalanguage. So, for example, the sentence \"Snow is white\" is true if and only if snow is white. Although many philosophers have interpreted, and continue to interpret, Tarski's theory as a deflationary theory, Popper refers to it as a theory in which \"is true\" is replaced with \"corresponds to the facts\". He bases this interpretation on the fact that examples such as the one described above refer to two things: assertions and the facts to which they refer. He identifies Tarski's formulation of the truth conditions of sentences as the introduction of a \"metalinguistic predicate\" and distinguishes the following cases:",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the part of a metalanguage?",
            "choices": [
                "Facts",
                "The Conditions For The Truth Of A Sentence",
                "Refer",
                "Theory"
            ],
            "answer": "The conditions for the truth of a sentence"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "According to this theory, the conditions for the truth of a sentence as well as the sentences themselves are part of a metalanguage. So, for example, the sentence \"Snow is white\" is true if and only if snow is white. Although many philosophers have interpreted, and continue to interpret, Tarski's theory as a deflationary theory, Popper refers to it as a theory in which \"is true\" is replaced with \"corresponds to the facts\". He bases this interpretation on the fact that examples such as the one described above refer to two things: assertions and the facts to which they refer. He identifies Tarski's formulation of the truth conditions of sentences as the introduction of a \"metalinguistic predicate\" and distinguishes the following cases:",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "Popper believes Tarski's theory is a metalanguage theory in which \"is true\" is replaced with \"corresponds to what?\"",
            "choices": [
                "Theory",
                "Refer",
                "Conditions",
                "The Facts"
            ],
            "answer": "The facts"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "According to this theory, the conditions for the truth of a sentence as well as the sentences themselves are part of a metalanguage. So, for example, the sentence \"Snow is white\" is true if and only if snow is white. Although many philosophers have interpreted, and continue to interpret, Tarski's theory as a deflationary theory, Popper refers to it as a theory in which \"is true\" is replaced with \"corresponds to the facts\". He bases this interpretation on the fact that examples such as the one described above refer to two things: assertions and the facts to which they refer. He identifies Tarski's formulation of the truth conditions of sentences as the introduction of a \"metalinguistic predicate\" and distinguishes the following cases:",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "Popper believes that the conditions for the truth of what are part of a metalanguage as well as the sentences themselves.",
            "choices": [
                "Conditions",
                "A Sentence",
                "Facts",
                "Theory"
            ],
            "answer": "A sentence"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "According to this theory, the conditions for the truth of a sentence as well as the sentences themselves are part of a metalanguage. So, for example, the sentence \"Snow is white\" is true if and only if snow is white. Although many philosophers have interpreted, and continue to interpret, Tarski's theory as a deflationary theory, Popper refers to it as a theory in which \"is true\" is replaced with \"corresponds to the facts\". He bases this interpretation on the fact that examples such as the one described above refer to two things: assertions and the facts to which they refer. He identifies Tarski's formulation of the truth conditions of sentences as the introduction of a \"metalinguistic predicate\" and distinguishes the following cases:",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the only condition for the truth of a sentence that Tarski's theory states is true?",
            "choices": [
                "Theory",
                "Conditions",
                "If Snow Is White",
                "Facts"
            ],
            "answer": "If snow is white"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In 1867, the university opened the first private nonsectarian law school west of the Mississippi River. By 1882, Washington University had expanded to numerous departments, which were housed in various buildings across St. Louis. Medical classes were first held at Washington University in 1891 after the St. Louis Medical College decided to affiliate with the University, establishing the School of Medicine. During the 1890s, Robert Sommers Brookings, the president of the Board of Trustees, undertook the tasks of reorganizing the university's finances, putting them onto a sound foundation, and buying land for a new campus.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What institution opened the first nonsectarian law school west of the Mississippi River?",
            "choices": [
                "Brandeis",
                "Laurier",
                "Yufa",
                "The University"
            ],
            "answer": "The university"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In 1867, the university opened the first private nonsectarian law school west of the Mississippi River. By 1882, Washington University had expanded to numerous departments, which were housed in various buildings across St. Louis. Medical classes were first held at Washington University in 1891 after the St. Louis Medical College decided to affiliate with the University, establishing the School of Medicine. During the 1890s, Robert Sommers Brookings, the president of the Board of Trustees, undertook the tasks of reorganizing the university's finances, putting them onto a sound foundation, and buying land for a new campus.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the name of the private nonsectarian law school that Washington University opened in 1867?",
            "choices": [
                "Medical",
                "University",
                "The First Private Nonsectarian Law School West Of The Mississippi River",
                "Louis"
            ],
            "answer": "The first private nonsectarian law school west of the mississippi river"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In 1867, the university opened the first private nonsectarian law school west of the Mississippi River. By 1882, Washington University had expanded to numerous departments, which were housed in various buildings across St. Louis. Medical classes were first held at Washington University in 1891 after the St. Louis Medical College decided to affiliate with the University, establishing the School of Medicine. During the 1890s, Robert Sommers Brookings, the president of the Board of Trustees, undertook the tasks of reorganizing the university's finances, putting them onto a sound foundation, and buying land for a new campus.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "When did Washington University begin expanding to numerous departments?",
            "choices": [
                "1882",
                "1922",
                "1790",
                "1950"
            ],
            "answer": "1882"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In 1867, the university opened the first private nonsectarian law school west of the Mississippi River. By 1882, Washington University had expanded to numerous departments, which were housed in various buildings across St. Louis. Medical classes were first held at Washington University in 1891 after the St. Louis Medical College decided to affiliate with the University, establishing the School of Medicine. During the 1890s, Robert Sommers Brookings, the president of the Board of Trustees, undertook the tasks of reorganizing the university's finances, putting them onto a sound foundation, and buying land for a new campus.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "When did Robert Sommers Brookings become president of the Board of Trustees?",
            "choices": [
                "University",
                "1890S",
                "Late 19Th Century",
                "Mid-1800S"
            ],
            "answer": "1890s"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In 1867, the university opened the first private nonsectarian law school west of the Mississippi River. By 1882, Washington University had expanded to numerous departments, which were housed in various buildings across St. Louis. Medical classes were first held at Washington University in 1891 after the St. Louis Medical College decided to affiliate with the University, establishing the School of Medicine. During the 1890s, Robert Sommers Brookings, the president of the Board of Trustees, undertook the tasks of reorganizing the university's finances, putting them onto a sound foundation, and buying land for a new campus.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "When were medical classes first held at Washington University?",
            "choices": [
                "1567",
                "1923",
                "1891",
                "1784"
            ],
            "answer": "1891"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "As of 2014, the wind industry in the USA is able to produce more power at lower cost by using taller wind turbines with longer blades, capturing the faster winds at higher elevations. This has opened up new opportunities and in Indiana, Michigan, and Ohio, the price of power from wind turbines built 300 feet to 400 feet above the ground can now compete with conventional fossil fuels like coal. Prices have fallen to about 4 cents per kilowatt-hour in some cases and utilities have been increasing the amount of wind energy in their portfolio, saying it is their cheapest option.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What industry is able to produce more power at lower cost?",
            "choices": [
                "Wind Industry",
                "Power",
                "Turbines",
                "Feet"
            ],
            "answer": "Wind industry"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "As of 2014, the wind industry in the USA is able to produce more power at lower cost by using taller wind turbines with longer blades, capturing the faster winds at higher elevations. This has opened up new opportunities and in Indiana, Michigan, and Ohio, the price of power from wind turbines built 300 feet to 400 feet above the ground can now compete with conventional fossil fuels like coal. Prices have fallen to about 4 cents per kilowatt-hour in some cases and utilities have been increasing the amount of wind energy in their portfolio, saying it is their cheapest option.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "How high are wind turbines in Indiana?",
            "choices": [
                "Power",
                "Wind",
                "400 Feet",
                "Turbines"
            ],
            "answer": "400 feet"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "As of 2014, the wind industry in the USA is able to produce more power at lower cost by using taller wind turbines with longer blades, capturing the faster winds at higher elevations. This has opened up new opportunities and in Indiana, Michigan, and Ohio, the price of power from wind turbines built 300 feet to 400 feet above the ground can now compete with conventional fossil fuels like coal. Prices have fallen to about 4 cents per kilowatt-hour in some cases and utilities have been increasing the amount of wind energy in their portfolio, saying it is their cheapest option.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is produced by taller wind turbines?",
            "choices": [
                "Feet",
                "Faster Winds",
                "Turbines",
                "Wind"
            ],
            "answer": "Faster winds"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "As of 2014, the wind industry in the USA is able to produce more power at lower cost by using taller wind turbines with longer blades, capturing the faster winds at higher elevations. This has opened up new opportunities and in Indiana, Michigan, and Ohio, the price of power from wind turbines built 300 feet to 400 feet above the ground can now compete with conventional fossil fuels like coal. Prices have fallen to about 4 cents per kilowatt-hour in some cases and utilities have been increasing the amount of wind energy in their portfolio, saying it is their cheapest option.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What type of wind turbines are used in the US to produce more power at lower cost?",
            "choices": [
                "Taller",
                "Boobs",
                "Ier",
                "Billy"
            ],
            "answer": "Taller"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "As of 2014, the wind industry in the USA is able to produce more power at lower cost by using taller wind turbines with longer blades, capturing the faster winds at higher elevations. This has opened up new opportunities and in Indiana, Michigan, and Ohio, the price of power from wind turbines built 300 feet to 400 feet above the ground can now compete with conventional fossil fuels like coal. Prices have fallen to about 4 cents per kilowatt-hour in some cases and utilities have been increasing the amount of wind energy in their portfolio, saying it is their cheapest option.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "When did the US wind industry begin to produce more power at lower cost?",
            "choices": [
                "2014/15",
                "2014",
                "2013/2014",
                "2009"
            ],
            "answer": "2014"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "passage": "The sky is usually clear above the desert and the sunshine duration is extremely high everywhere in the Sahara. Most of the desert enjoys more than 3,600 h of bright sunshine annually or over 82% of the time and a wide area in the eastern part experiences in excess of 4,000 h of bright sunshine a year or over 91% of the time, and the highest values are very close to the theoretical maximum value. A value of 4,300 h or 98% of the time would be recorded in Upper Egypt (Aswan, Luxor) and in the Nubian Desert (Wadi Halfa). The annual average direct solar irradiation is around 2,800 kWh/(m2 year) in the Great Desert. The Sahara has a huge potential for solar energy production. The constantly high position of the sun, the extremely low relative humidity, the lack of vegetation and rainfall make the Great Desert the hottest continuously large area worldwide and certainly the hottest place on Earth during summertime in some spots. The average high temperature exceeds 38 \u00b0C (100.4 \u00b0F) - 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) during the hottest month nearly everywhere in the desert except at very high mountainous areas. The highest officially recorded average high temperature was 47 \u00b0C (116.6 \u00b0F) in a remote desert town in the Algerian Desert called Bou Bernous with an elevation of 378 meters above sea level. It's the world's highest recorded average high temperature and only Death Valley, California rivals it. Other hot spots in Algeria such as Adrar, Timimoun, In Salah, Ouallene, Aoulef, Reggane with an elevation between 200 and 400 meters above sea level get slightly lower summer average highs around 46 \u00b0C (114.8 \u00b0F) during the hottest months of the year. Salah, well known in Algeria for its extreme heat, has an average high temperature of 43.8 \u00b0C (110.8 \u00b0F), 46.4 \u00b0C (115.5 \u00b0F), 45.5 (113.9 \u00b0F). Furthermore, 41.9 \u00b0C (107.4 \u00b0F) in June, July, August and September. In fact, there are even hotter spots in the Sahara, but they are located in extremely remote areas, especially in the Azalai, lying in northern Mali. The major part of the desert experiences around 3 \u2013 5 months when the average high strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F). The southern central part of the desert experiences up to 6 \u2013 7 months when the average high temperature strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) which shows the constancy and the length of the really hot season in the Sahara. Some examples of this are Bilma, Niger and Faya-Largeau, Chad. The annual average daily temperature exceeds 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F) everywhere and can approach 30 \u00b0C (86 \u00b0F) in the hottest regions year-round. However, most of the desert has a value in excess of 25 \u00b0C (77 \u00b0F). The sand and ground temperatures are even more extreme. During daytime, the sand temperature is extremely high as it can easily reach 80 \u00b0C (176 \u00b0F) or more. A sand temperature of 83.5 \u00b0C (182.3 \u00b0F) has been recorded in Port Sudan. Ground temperatures of 72 \u00b0C (161.6 \u00b0F) have been recorded in the Adrar of Mauritania and a value of 75 \u00b0C (167 \u00b0F) has been measured in Borkou, northern Chad. Due to lack of cloud cover and very low humidity, the desert usually features high diurnal temperature variations between days and nights. However, it's a myth that the nights are cold after extremely hot days in the Sahara. The average diurnal temperature range is typically between 13 \u00b0C (55.4 \u00b0F) and 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F). The lowest values are found along the coastal regions due to high humidity and are often even lower than 10 \u00b0C (50 \u00b0F), while the highest values are found in inland desert areas where the humidity is the lowest, mainly in the southern Sahara. Still, it's true that winter nights can be cold as it can drop to the freezing point and even below, especially in high-elevation areas.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What part of the Sahara is usually clear above the sky?",
            "choices": [
                "Tundra",
                "Desert",
                "Far North",
                "Dense Forest"
            ],
            "answer": "Desert"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "passage": "The sky is usually clear above the desert and the sunshine duration is extremely high everywhere in the Sahara. Most of the desert enjoys more than 3,600 h of bright sunshine annually or over 82% of the time and a wide area in the eastern part experiences in excess of 4,000 h of bright sunshine a year or over 91% of the time, and the highest values are very close to the theoretical maximum value. A value of 4,300 h or 98% of the time would be recorded in Upper Egypt (Aswan, Luxor) and in the Nubian Desert (Wadi Halfa). The annual average direct solar irradiation is around 2,800 kWh/(m2 year) in the Great Desert. The Sahara has a huge potential for solar energy production. The constantly high position of the sun, the extremely low relative humidity, the lack of vegetation and rainfall make the Great Desert the hottest continuously large area worldwide and certainly the hottest place on Earth during summertime in some spots. The average high temperature exceeds 38 \u00b0C (100.4 \u00b0F) - 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) during the hottest month nearly everywhere in the desert except at very high mountainous areas. The highest officially recorded average high temperature was 47 \u00b0C (116.6 \u00b0F) in a remote desert town in the Algerian Desert called Bou Bernous with an elevation of 378 meters above sea level. It's the world's highest recorded average high temperature and only Death Valley, California rivals it. Other hot spots in Algeria such as Adrar, Timimoun, In Salah, Ouallene, Aoulef, Reggane with an elevation between 200 and 400 meters above sea level get slightly lower summer average highs around 46 \u00b0C (114.8 \u00b0F) during the hottest months of the year. Salah, well known in Algeria for its extreme heat, has an average high temperature of 43.8 \u00b0C (110.8 \u00b0F), 46.4 \u00b0C (115.5 \u00b0F), 45.5 (113.9 \u00b0F). Furthermore, 41.9 \u00b0C (107.4 \u00b0F) in June, July, August and September. In fact, there are even hotter spots in the Sahara, but they are located in extremely remote areas, especially in the Azalai, lying in northern Mali. The major part of the desert experiences around 3 \u2013 5 months when the average high strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F). The southern central part of the desert experiences up to 6 \u2013 7 months when the average high temperature strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) which shows the constancy and the length of the really hot season in the Sahara. Some examples of this are Bilma, Niger and Faya-Largeau, Chad. The annual average daily temperature exceeds 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F) everywhere and can approach 30 \u00b0C (86 \u00b0F) in the hottest regions year-round. However, most of the desert has a value in excess of 25 \u00b0C (77 \u00b0F). The sand and ground temperatures are even more extreme. During daytime, the sand temperature is extremely high as it can easily reach 80 \u00b0C (176 \u00b0F) or more. A sand temperature of 83.5 \u00b0C (182.3 \u00b0F) has been recorded in Port Sudan. Ground temperatures of 72 \u00b0C (161.6 \u00b0F) have been recorded in the Adrar of Mauritania and a value of 75 \u00b0C (167 \u00b0F) has been measured in Borkou, northern Chad. Due to lack of cloud cover and very low humidity, the desert usually features high diurnal temperature variations between days and nights. However, it's a myth that the nights are cold after extremely hot days in the Sahara. The average diurnal temperature range is typically between 13 \u00b0C (55.4 \u00b0F) and 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F). The lowest values are found along the coastal regions due to high humidity and are often even lower than 10 \u00b0C (50 \u00b0F), while the highest values are found in inland desert areas where the humidity is the lowest, mainly in the southern Sahara. Still, it's true that winter nights can be cold as it can drop to the freezing point and even below, especially in high-elevation areas.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the duration of the sun in the Sahara?",
            "choices": [
                "Desert",
                "Extremely High",
                "Temperature",
                "Average"
            ],
            "answer": "Extremely high"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "passage": "The sky is usually clear above the desert and the sunshine duration is extremely high everywhere in the Sahara. Most of the desert enjoys more than 3,600 h of bright sunshine annually or over 82% of the time and a wide area in the eastern part experiences in excess of 4,000 h of bright sunshine a year or over 91% of the time, and the highest values are very close to the theoretical maximum value. A value of 4,300 h or 98% of the time would be recorded in Upper Egypt (Aswan, Luxor) and in the Nubian Desert (Wadi Halfa). The annual average direct solar irradiation is around 2,800 kWh/(m2 year) in the Great Desert. The Sahara has a huge potential for solar energy production. The constantly high position of the sun, the extremely low relative humidity, the lack of vegetation and rainfall make the Great Desert the hottest continuously large area worldwide and certainly the hottest place on Earth during summertime in some spots. The average high temperature exceeds 38 \u00b0C (100.4 \u00b0F) - 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) during the hottest month nearly everywhere in the desert except at very high mountainous areas. The highest officially recorded average high temperature was 47 \u00b0C (116.6 \u00b0F) in a remote desert town in the Algerian Desert called Bou Bernous with an elevation of 378 meters above sea level. It's the world's highest recorded average high temperature and only Death Valley, California rivals it. Other hot spots in Algeria such as Adrar, Timimoun, In Salah, Ouallene, Aoulef, Reggane with an elevation between 200 and 400 meters above sea level get slightly lower summer average highs around 46 \u00b0C (114.8 \u00b0F) during the hottest months of the year. Salah, well known in Algeria for its extreme heat, has an average high temperature of 43.8 \u00b0C (110.8 \u00b0F), 46.4 \u00b0C (115.5 \u00b0F), 45.5 (113.9 \u00b0F). Furthermore, 41.9 \u00b0C (107.4 \u00b0F) in June, July, August and September. In fact, there are even hotter spots in the Sahara, but they are located in extremely remote areas, especially in the Azalai, lying in northern Mali. The major part of the desert experiences around 3 \u2013 5 months when the average high strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F). The southern central part of the desert experiences up to 6 \u2013 7 months when the average high temperature strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) which shows the constancy and the length of the really hot season in the Sahara. Some examples of this are Bilma, Niger and Faya-Largeau, Chad. The annual average daily temperature exceeds 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F) everywhere and can approach 30 \u00b0C (86 \u00b0F) in the hottest regions year-round. However, most of the desert has a value in excess of 25 \u00b0C (77 \u00b0F). The sand and ground temperatures are even more extreme. During daytime, the sand temperature is extremely high as it can easily reach 80 \u00b0C (176 \u00b0F) or more. A sand temperature of 83.5 \u00b0C (182.3 \u00b0F) has been recorded in Port Sudan. Ground temperatures of 72 \u00b0C (161.6 \u00b0F) have been recorded in the Adrar of Mauritania and a value of 75 \u00b0C (167 \u00b0F) has been measured in Borkou, northern Chad. Due to lack of cloud cover and very low humidity, the desert usually features high diurnal temperature variations between days and nights. However, it's a myth that the nights are cold after extremely hot days in the Sahara. The average diurnal temperature range is typically between 13 \u00b0C (55.4 \u00b0F) and 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F). The lowest values are found along the coastal regions due to high humidity and are often even lower than 10 \u00b0C (50 \u00b0F), while the highest values are found in inland desert areas where the humidity is the lowest, mainly in the southern Sahara. Still, it's true that winter nights can be cold as it can drop to the freezing point and even below, especially in high-elevation areas.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the annual direct solar irradiation in the Great Desert?",
            "choices": [
                "Desert",
                "2,800 Kwh/(M2 Year)",
                "Temperature",
                "High"
            ],
            "answer": "2,800 kwh/(m2 year)"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "passage": "The sky is usually clear above the desert and the sunshine duration is extremely high everywhere in the Sahara. Most of the desert enjoys more than 3,600 h of bright sunshine annually or over 82% of the time and a wide area in the eastern part experiences in excess of 4,000 h of bright sunshine a year or over 91% of the time, and the highest values are very close to the theoretical maximum value. A value of 4,300 h or 98% of the time would be recorded in Upper Egypt (Aswan, Luxor) and in the Nubian Desert (Wadi Halfa). The annual average direct solar irradiation is around 2,800 kWh/(m2 year) in the Great Desert. The Sahara has a huge potential for solar energy production. The constantly high position of the sun, the extremely low relative humidity, the lack of vegetation and rainfall make the Great Desert the hottest continuously large area worldwide and certainly the hottest place on Earth during summertime in some spots. The average high temperature exceeds 38 \u00b0C (100.4 \u00b0F) - 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) during the hottest month nearly everywhere in the desert except at very high mountainous areas. The highest officially recorded average high temperature was 47 \u00b0C (116.6 \u00b0F) in a remote desert town in the Algerian Desert called Bou Bernous with an elevation of 378 meters above sea level. It's the world's highest recorded average high temperature and only Death Valley, California rivals it. Other hot spots in Algeria such as Adrar, Timimoun, In Salah, Ouallene, Aoulef, Reggane with an elevation between 200 and 400 meters above sea level get slightly lower summer average highs around 46 \u00b0C (114.8 \u00b0F) during the hottest months of the year. Salah, well known in Algeria for its extreme heat, has an average high temperature of 43.8 \u00b0C (110.8 \u00b0F), 46.4 \u00b0C (115.5 \u00b0F), 45.5 (113.9 \u00b0F). Furthermore, 41.9 \u00b0C (107.4 \u00b0F) in June, July, August and September. In fact, there are even hotter spots in the Sahara, but they are located in extremely remote areas, especially in the Azalai, lying in northern Mali. The major part of the desert experiences around 3 \u2013 5 months when the average high strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F). The southern central part of the desert experiences up to 6 \u2013 7 months when the average high temperature strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) which shows the constancy and the length of the really hot season in the Sahara. Some examples of this are Bilma, Niger and Faya-Largeau, Chad. The annual average daily temperature exceeds 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F) everywhere and can approach 30 \u00b0C (86 \u00b0F) in the hottest regions year-round. However, most of the desert has a value in excess of 25 \u00b0C (77 \u00b0F). The sand and ground temperatures are even more extreme. During daytime, the sand temperature is extremely high as it can easily reach 80 \u00b0C (176 \u00b0F) or more. A sand temperature of 83.5 \u00b0C (182.3 \u00b0F) has been recorded in Port Sudan. Ground temperatures of 72 \u00b0C (161.6 \u00b0F) have been recorded in the Adrar of Mauritania and a value of 75 \u00b0C (167 \u00b0F) has been measured in Borkou, northern Chad. Due to lack of cloud cover and very low humidity, the desert usually features high diurnal temperature variations between days and nights. However, it's a myth that the nights are cold after extremely hot days in the Sahara. The average diurnal temperature range is typically between 13 \u00b0C (55.4 \u00b0F) and 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F). The lowest values are found along the coastal regions due to high humidity and are often even lower than 10 \u00b0C (50 \u00b0F), while the highest values are found in inland desert areas where the humidity is the lowest, mainly in the southern Sahara. Still, it's true that winter nights can be cold as it can drop to the freezing point and even below, especially in high-elevation areas.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the average high temperature in the desert?",
            "choices": [
                "47 \u00b0C",
                "Desert",
                "High",
                "Average"
            ],
            "answer": "47 \u00b0c"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "passage": "The sky is usually clear above the desert and the sunshine duration is extremely high everywhere in the Sahara. Most of the desert enjoys more than 3,600 h of bright sunshine annually or over 82% of the time and a wide area in the eastern part experiences in excess of 4,000 h of bright sunshine a year or over 91% of the time, and the highest values are very close to the theoretical maximum value. A value of 4,300 h or 98% of the time would be recorded in Upper Egypt (Aswan, Luxor) and in the Nubian Desert (Wadi Halfa). The annual average direct solar irradiation is around 2,800 kWh/(m2 year) in the Great Desert. The Sahara has a huge potential for solar energy production. The constantly high position of the sun, the extremely low relative humidity, the lack of vegetation and rainfall make the Great Desert the hottest continuously large area worldwide and certainly the hottest place on Earth during summertime in some spots. The average high temperature exceeds 38 \u00b0C (100.4 \u00b0F) - 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) during the hottest month nearly everywhere in the desert except at very high mountainous areas. The highest officially recorded average high temperature was 47 \u00b0C (116.6 \u00b0F) in a remote desert town in the Algerian Desert called Bou Bernous with an elevation of 378 meters above sea level. It's the world's highest recorded average high temperature and only Death Valley, California rivals it. Other hot spots in Algeria such as Adrar, Timimoun, In Salah, Ouallene, Aoulef, Reggane with an elevation between 200 and 400 meters above sea level get slightly lower summer average highs around 46 \u00b0C (114.8 \u00b0F) during the hottest months of the year. Salah, well known in Algeria for its extreme heat, has an average high temperature of 43.8 \u00b0C (110.8 \u00b0F), 46.4 \u00b0C (115.5 \u00b0F), 45.5 (113.9 \u00b0F). Furthermore, 41.9 \u00b0C (107.4 \u00b0F) in June, July, August and September. In fact, there are even hotter spots in the Sahara, but they are located in extremely remote areas, especially in the Azalai, lying in northern Mali. The major part of the desert experiences around 3 \u2013 5 months when the average high strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F). The southern central part of the desert experiences up to 6 \u2013 7 months when the average high temperature strictly exceeds 40 \u00b0C (104 \u00b0F) which shows the constancy and the length of the really hot season in the Sahara. Some examples of this are Bilma, Niger and Faya-Largeau, Chad. The annual average daily temperature exceeds 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F) everywhere and can approach 30 \u00b0C (86 \u00b0F) in the hottest regions year-round. However, most of the desert has a value in excess of 25 \u00b0C (77 \u00b0F). The sand and ground temperatures are even more extreme. During daytime, the sand temperature is extremely high as it can easily reach 80 \u00b0C (176 \u00b0F) or more. A sand temperature of 83.5 \u00b0C (182.3 \u00b0F) has been recorded in Port Sudan. Ground temperatures of 72 \u00b0C (161.6 \u00b0F) have been recorded in the Adrar of Mauritania and a value of 75 \u00b0C (167 \u00b0F) has been measured in Borkou, northern Chad. Due to lack of cloud cover and very low humidity, the desert usually features high diurnal temperature variations between days and nights. However, it's a myth that the nights are cold after extremely hot days in the Sahara. The average diurnal temperature range is typically between 13 \u00b0C (55.4 \u00b0F) and 20 \u00b0C (68 \u00b0F). The lowest values are found along the coastal regions due to high humidity and are often even lower than 10 \u00b0C (50 \u00b0F), while the highest values are found in inland desert areas where the humidity is the lowest, mainly in the southern Sahara. Still, it's true that winter nights can be cold as it can drop to the freezing point and even below, especially in high-elevation areas.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the Great Desert's constant temperature?",
            "choices": [
                "High",
                "104 \u00b0F",
                "Desert",
                "Average"
            ],
            "answer": "104 \u00b0f"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In Thailand, a kingdom that has had a constitution since the initial attempt to overthrow the absolute monarchy system in 1932, the rule of law has been more of a principle than actual practice.[citation needed] Ancient prejudices and political bias have been present in the three branches of government with each of their foundings, and justice has been processed formally according to the law but in fact more closely aligned with royalist principles that are still advocated in the 21st century.[citation needed] In November 2013, Thailand faced still further threats to the rule of law when the executive branch rejected a supreme court decision over how to select senators.[citation needed]",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is needed to explain the rule of law in Thailand?",
            "choices": [
                "Rule",
                "Law",
                "Ancient Prejudices And Political Bias",
                "Needed"
            ],
            "answer": "Ancient prejudices and political bias"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In Thailand, a kingdom that has had a constitution since the initial attempt to overthrow the absolute monarchy system in 1932, the rule of law has been more of a principle than actual practice.[citation needed] Ancient prejudices and political bias have been present in the three branches of government with each of their foundings, and justice has been processed formally according to the law but in fact more closely aligned with royalist principles that are still advocated in the 21st century.[citation needed] In November 2013, Thailand faced still further threats to the rule of law when the executive branch rejected a supreme court decision over how to select senators.[citation needed]",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What rule has been more of a principle than actual practice in Thailand?",
            "choices": [
                "Rule",
                "Needed",
                "Citation",
                "Rule Of Law"
            ],
            "answer": "Rule of law"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In Thailand, a kingdom that has had a constitution since the initial attempt to overthrow the absolute monarchy system in 1932, the rule of law has been more of a principle than actual practice.[citation needed] Ancient prejudices and political bias have been present in the three branches of government with each of their foundings, and justice has been processed formally according to the law but in fact more closely aligned with royalist principles that are still advocated in the 21st century.[citation needed] In November 2013, Thailand faced still further threats to the rule of law when the executive branch rejected a supreme court decision over how to select senators.[citation needed]",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the constitution of Thailand?",
            "choices": [
                "Thailand",
                "Bali",
                "Macau",
                "New Zealand"
            ],
            "answer": "Thailand"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In Thailand, a kingdom that has had a constitution since the initial attempt to overthrow the absolute monarchy system in 1932, the rule of law has been more of a principle than actual practice.[citation needed] Ancient prejudices and political bias have been present in the three branches of government with each of their foundings, and justice has been processed formally according to the law but in fact more closely aligned with royalist principles that are still advocated in the 21st century.[citation needed] In November 2013, Thailand faced still further threats to the rule of law when the executive branch rejected a supreme court decision over how to select senators.[citation needed]",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "When did Thailand first attempt to overthrow the absolute monarchy system?",
            "choices": [
                "1947",
                "1882",
                "1932",
                "1960"
            ],
            "answer": "1932"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "In Thailand, a kingdom that has had a constitution since the initial attempt to overthrow the absolute monarchy system in 1932, the rule of law has been more of a principle than actual practice.[citation needed] Ancient prejudices and political bias have been present in the three branches of government with each of their foundings, and justice has been processed formally according to the law but in fact more closely aligned with royalist principles that are still advocated in the 21st century.[citation needed] In November 2013, Thailand faced still further threats to the rule of law when the executive branch rejected a supreme court decision over how to select senators.[citation needed]",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "In what year did Thailand face threats to the rule of law?",
            "choices": [
                "2009",
                "1999",
                "2013/2014",
                "2013"
            ],
            "answer": "2013"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "Following his defeat in the civil war, Gaddafi's system of governance was dismantled and replaced under the interim government of the NTC, who legalised trade unions and freedom of the press. In July 2012, elections were held to form a new General National Congress (GNC), who officially took over governance from the NTC in August. The GNC proceeded to elect Mohammed Magariaf as president of the chamber, and then voted Mustafa A.G. Abushagur as Prime Minister; when Abushagar failed to gain congressional approval, the GNC instead elected Ali Zeidan to the position. In January 2013, the GNC officially renamed the Jamahiriyah as the \"State of Libya\".",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the name of the Jamahiriyah?",
            "choices": [
                "Officially",
                "Governance",
                "The \"State Of Libya\"",
                "Ntc"
            ],
            "answer": "The \"state of libya\""
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "Following his defeat in the civil war, Gaddafi's system of governance was dismantled and replaced under the interim government of the NTC, who legalised trade unions and freedom of the press. In July 2012, elections were held to form a new General National Congress (GNC), who officially took over governance from the NTC in August. The GNC proceeded to elect Mohammed Magariaf as president of the chamber, and then voted Mustafa A.G. Abushagur as Prime Minister; when Abushagar failed to gain congressional approval, the GNC instead elected Ali Zeidan to the position. In January 2013, the GNC officially renamed the Jamahiriyah as the \"State of Libya\".",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What system did Gaddafi have in place after his defeat in the civil war?",
            "choices": [
                "Officially",
                "Gnc",
                "Ntc",
                "System Of Governance"
            ],
            "answer": "System of governance"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "Following his defeat in the civil war, Gaddafi's system of governance was dismantled and replaced under the interim government of the NTC, who legalised trade unions and freedom of the press. In July 2012, elections were held to form a new General National Congress (GNC), who officially took over governance from the NTC in August. The GNC proceeded to elect Mohammed Magariaf as president of the chamber, and then voted Mustafa A.G. Abushagur as Prime Minister; when Abushagar failed to gain congressional approval, the GNC instead elected Ali Zeidan to the position. In January 2013, the GNC officially renamed the Jamahiriyah as the \"State of Libya\".",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "How did the GNC take over from the NTC?",
            "choices": [
                "Ntc",
                "Ali Zeidan",
                "Gnc",
                "Governance"
            ],
            "answer": "Ali zeidan"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "Following his defeat in the civil war, Gaddafi's system of governance was dismantled and replaced under the interim government of the NTC, who legalised trade unions and freedom of the press. In July 2012, elections were held to form a new General National Congress (GNC), who officially took over governance from the NTC in August. The GNC proceeded to elect Mohammed Magariaf as president of the chamber, and then voted Mustafa A.G. Abushagur as Prime Minister; when Abushagar failed to gain congressional approval, the GNC instead elected Ali Zeidan to the position. In January 2013, the GNC officially renamed the Jamahiriyah as the \"State of Libya\".",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "In what year did the GNC form?",
            "choices": [
                "1997",
                "09",
                "2012",
                "2008"
            ],
            "answer": "2012"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "Following his defeat in the civil war, Gaddafi's system of governance was dismantled and replaced under the interim government of the NTC, who legalised trade unions and freedom of the press. In July 2012, elections were held to form a new General National Congress (GNC), who officially took over governance from the NTC in August. The GNC proceeded to elect Mohammed Magariaf as president of the chamber, and then voted Mustafa A.G. Abushagur as Prime Minister; when Abushagar failed to gain congressional approval, the GNC instead elected Ali Zeidan to the position. In January 2013, the GNC officially renamed the Jamahiriyah as the \"State of Libya\".",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "In what year did the GNC rename the Jamahiriyah as the \"State of Libya\"?",
            "choices": [
                "1999",
                "2009",
                "2013/2014",
                "2013"
            ],
            "answer": "2013"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "passage": "These ongoing efforts contributed to the formation of The Football Association (The FA) in 1863, which first met on the morning of 26 October 1863 at the Freemasons' Tavern in Great Queen Street, London. The only school to be represented on this occasion was Charterhouse. The Freemason's Tavern was the setting for five more meetings between October and December, which eventually produced the first comprehensive set of rules. At the final meeting, the first FA treasurer, the representative from Blackheath, withdrew his club from the FA over the removal of two draft rules at the previous meeting: the first allowed for running with the ball in hand; the second for obstructing such a run by hacking (kicking an opponent in the shins), tripping and holding. Other English rugby clubs followed this lead and did not join the FA and instead in 1871 formed the Rugby Football Union. The eleven remaining clubs, under the charge of Ebenezer Cobb Morley, went on to ratify the original thirteen laws of the game. These rules included handling of the ball by \"marks\" and the lack of a crossbar, rules which made it remarkably similar to Victorian rules football being developed at that time in Australia. The Sheffield FA played by its own rules until the 1870s with the FA absorbing some of its rules until there was little difference between the games.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the first comprehensive set of?",
            "choices": [
                "Football",
                "The Football Association (The Fa)",
                "1863",
                "Fa"
            ],
            "answer": "The football association (the fa)"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "passage": "These ongoing efforts contributed to the formation of The Football Association (The FA) in 1863, which first met on the morning of 26 October 1863 at the Freemasons' Tavern in Great Queen Street, London. The only school to be represented on this occasion was Charterhouse. The Freemason's Tavern was the setting for five more meetings between October and December, which eventually produced the first comprehensive set of rules. At the final meeting, the first FA treasurer, the representative from Blackheath, withdrew his club from the FA over the removal of two draft rules at the previous meeting: the first allowed for running with the ball in hand; the second for obstructing such a run by hacking (kicking an opponent in the shins), tripping and holding. Other English rugby clubs followed this lead and did not join the FA and instead in 1871 formed the Rugby Football Union. The eleven remaining clubs, under the charge of Ebenezer Cobb Morley, went on to ratify the original thirteen laws of the game. These rules included handling of the ball by \"marks\" and the lack of a crossbar, rules which made it remarkably similar to Victorian rules football being developed at that time in Australia. The Sheffield FA played by its own rules until the 1870s with the FA absorbing some of its rules until there was little difference between the games.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the first draft of rules for running with the ball in hand?",
            "choices": [
                "Football",
                "1863",
                "The First Allowed For Running With The Ball In Hand",
                "Rules"
            ],
            "answer": "The first allowed for running with the ball in hand"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "passage": "These ongoing efforts contributed to the formation of The Football Association (The FA) in 1863, which first met on the morning of 26 October 1863 at the Freemasons' Tavern in Great Queen Street, London. The only school to be represented on this occasion was Charterhouse. The Freemason's Tavern was the setting for five more meetings between October and December, which eventually produced the first comprehensive set of rules. At the final meeting, the first FA treasurer, the representative from Blackheath, withdrew his club from the FA over the removal of two draft rules at the previous meeting: the first allowed for running with the ball in hand; the second for obstructing such a run by hacking (kicking an opponent in the shins), tripping and holding. Other English rugby clubs followed this lead and did not join the FA and instead in 1871 formed the Rugby Football Union. The eleven remaining clubs, under the charge of Ebenezer Cobb Morley, went on to ratify the original thirteen laws of the game. These rules included handling of the ball by \"marks\" and the lack of a crossbar, rules which made it remarkably similar to Victorian rules football being developed at that time in Australia. The Sheffield FA played by its own rules until the 1870s with the FA absorbing some of its rules until there was little difference between the games.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the Victorian game called that was similar to the rules of rugby?",
            "choices": [
                "American Sports",
                "Gridiron",
                "Football",
                "Bball"
            ],
            "answer": "Football"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "passage": "These ongoing efforts contributed to the formation of The Football Association (The FA) in 1863, which first met on the morning of 26 October 1863 at the Freemasons' Tavern in Great Queen Street, London. The only school to be represented on this occasion was Charterhouse. The Freemason's Tavern was the setting for five more meetings between October and December, which eventually produced the first comprehensive set of rules. At the final meeting, the first FA treasurer, the representative from Blackheath, withdrew his club from the FA over the removal of two draft rules at the previous meeting: the first allowed for running with the ball in hand; the second for obstructing such a run by hacking (kicking an opponent in the shins), tripping and holding. Other English rugby clubs followed this lead and did not join the FA and instead in 1871 formed the Rugby Football Union. The eleven remaining clubs, under the charge of Ebenezer Cobb Morley, went on to ratify the original thirteen laws of the game. These rules included handling of the ball by \"marks\" and the lack of a crossbar, rules which made it remarkably similar to Victorian rules football being developed at that time in Australia. The Sheffield FA played by its own rules until the 1870s with the FA absorbing some of its rules until there was little difference between the games.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "When was the Football Association formed?",
            "choices": [
                "1890",
                "1801",
                "1912",
                "1863"
            ],
            "answer": "1863"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "passage": "These ongoing efforts contributed to the formation of The Football Association (The FA) in 1863, which first met on the morning of 26 October 1863 at the Freemasons' Tavern in Great Queen Street, London. The only school to be represented on this occasion was Charterhouse. The Freemason's Tavern was the setting for five more meetings between October and December, which eventually produced the first comprehensive set of rules. At the final meeting, the first FA treasurer, the representative from Blackheath, withdrew his club from the FA over the removal of two draft rules at the previous meeting: the first allowed for running with the ball in hand; the second for obstructing such a run by hacking (kicking an opponent in the shins), tripping and holding. Other English rugby clubs followed this lead and did not join the FA and instead in 1871 formed the Rugby Football Union. The eleven remaining clubs, under the charge of Ebenezer Cobb Morley, went on to ratify the original thirteen laws of the game. These rules included handling of the ball by \"marks\" and the lack of a crossbar, rules which made it remarkably similar to Victorian rules football being developed at that time in Australia. The Sheffield FA played by its own rules until the 1870s with the FA absorbing some of its rules until there was little difference between the games.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the foot association known as?",
            "choices": [
                "Fa",
                "Football",
                "The Football Association",
                "Rules"
            ],
            "answer": "The football association"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "A test given to new students by Stanford University Music Professor Jonathan Berger showed that student preference for MP3-quality music has risen each year. Berger said the students seem to prefer the 'sizzle' sounds that MP3s bring to music.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What type of music does Jonathan Berger say students prefer?",
            "choices": [
                "Bring",
                "Berger",
                "Students",
                "The'Sizzle' Sounds"
            ],
            "answer": "The'sizzle' sounds"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "A test given to new students by Stanford University Music Professor Jonathan Berger showed that student preference for MP3-quality music has risen each year. Berger said the students seem to prefer the 'sizzle' sounds that MP3s bring to music.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What is the preference for MP3 quality music?",
            "choices": [
                "The'Sizzle' Sounds",
                "Students",
                "Music",
                "Bring"
            ],
            "answer": "The'sizzle' sounds"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "A test given to new students by Stanford University Music Professor Jonathan Berger showed that student preference for MP3-quality music has risen each year. Berger said the students seem to prefer the 'sizzle' sounds that MP3s bring to music.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What type of students did Jonathan Berger test?",
            "choices": [
                "New Students",
                "Regular Classes",
                "Undergrads",
                "Upperclassmen"
            ],
            "answer": "New students"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "A test given to new students by Stanford University Music Professor Jonathan Berger showed that student preference for MP3-quality music has risen each year. Berger said the students seem to prefer the 'sizzle' sounds that MP3s bring to music.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What do students prefer about MP3s?",
            "choices": [
                "Sizzle",
                "Drippings",
                "Wok",
                "Grill"
            ],
            "answer": "Sizzle"
        }
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "passage": "A test given to new students by Stanford University Music Professor Jonathan Berger showed that student preference for MP3-quality music has risen each year. Berger said the students seem to prefer the 'sizzle' sounds that MP3s bring to music.",
        "questions-choices-answer": {
            "question": "What was the test done by Professor Jonathan Berger?",
            "choices": [
                "Student Preference For Mp3-Quality Music",
                "Berger",
                "Students",
                "Music"
            ],
            "answer": "Student preference for mp3-quality music"
        }
    }
]